hellomusic.com 2011-06-04

# HELLO MUSIC

Hello Music Privacy Policy

Hello Music Deals Privacy Policy

####  Hello Music Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of and was last updated on **January 20, 2010**.

This privacy policy (this **"Privacy Policy"** ) is designed to inform you about the type of information that Hello Music ( **"we,"** **"us,"** or **"our"** ) may gather or collect from you in connection with your use of this site (this **"Site"** ). It also explains the conditions under which we use and disclose that information, and your rights in relation to that information.

The procedures for modifying or changing this Privacy Policy in the future are discussed in Section 6 of this document.

↑ Back to Top

This Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

↑ Back to Top

We collect both Non-Personally-Identifying Information and Personally-Identifying Information from you. **"Non–Personally–Identifying Information"** is information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity. **"Personally–Identifying Information,"** by contrast, is information such as a name or email address that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person or entity.

A. Gathering Non-Personally-Identifying Information

(i) Web Browsers

Like most site operators, we gather Non-Personally-Identifying Information from you of the sort that web browsers, depending on their settings, may make available. That information includes your Internet Protocol ( **"IP"** ) address, operating system and browser type, and the locations of the web pages you view right before arriving at, while navigating and immediately after leaving this Site.

(ii) Web Cookies

A **"Web Cookie"** is a string of information that a site stores on your computer, and your browser provides to this Site, each time you submit a query to this Site. We may use Web Cookies to track the pages that you visit during each Site session, both to help us improve your experience and to help us understand how this Site is being used.

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE WEB COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSER TO REFUSE WEB COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THIS SITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THIS SITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF WEB COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE WEB COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

(iii) Web Beacons

A **"Web Beacon"** is an object that is embedded in a web page. It is usually invisible to you but allows site operators to check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email communication. We may place Web Beacons on pages of this Site and in emails we send to you.

You may not decline Web Beacons. However, they may be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.

(iv) Third Parties' Use of Web Beacons and Web Cookies

This Site may include third-party advertising, links to other sites, and other content from third party businesses. The content posted by these parties will be reasonably identifiable as coming from a third party. These third-party sites, businesses, and advertisers, or advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use Web Beacons and Web Cookies to measure the effectiveness of their ads, personalize or optimize advertising content and to track users who link from their respective sites to this Site, but this third party technology does not permit them to access your Personal Information.

We do not have access to or control over Web Beacons or Web Cookies that these third parties may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites or businesses are not covered by this Privacy Policy but are covered by their respective privacy policies as is described in more detail in Section 5 below.

Some third party advertising companies may provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology. For more information about these partners and links to their privacy policies, please view each third party’s site.

B. Use of Non-Personally-Identifying Information

We analyze Non–Personally–Identifying Information gathered from users of this Site to help us better understand how this Site is being used. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, we are able to better design this Site to improve your experiences, both in terms of content and ease of use. We link information gathered using Non-Personally-Identifying Information to Personally-Identifying Information.

C. Disclosure of Non-Personally-Identifying Information

From time to time, we may also release the Non–Personally–Identifying Information gathered from Site users in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of this Site.

↑ Back to Top

As defined above, Personally-Identifying Information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity. We will only collect Personally-Identifying Information that you knowingly submit to us. We will not disclose your Personally-Identifying Information to third parties unless we obtain your permission to do so at the time we collect it, except as set forth below:

A. Collecting Personally-Identifying Information from Site Users

i. Registration and Other Information Provided to Us

When you register with this Site, you may be asked to disclose Personally–Identifying Information. You may also choose to submit Personally-Identifying Information to us when you send us an email, set up a profile or use any interactive features and services that we may make available from time to time on this Site.

ii. Modifying Your Profile

If you are an artist, you may modify your personal profile at any time by going to the home page of the Site ([www.hellomusic.com](http://www.hellomusic.com/)), clicking "login" and entering your user ID and password. Then, select the profile you wish modify by clicking on the corresponding tab on the top of the page. Finally, click "Edit Profile," and you may change any field in the profile.

If you are a screener, you may modify your personal profile at any time by going to the home page of the Site ([www.hellomusic.com](http://www.hellomusic.com/)), clicking "login" and entering your user ID and password. Then, select your screener profile by clicking on the corresponding tab on the top of the page. Finally, click "Edit Profile," and you may change any field in the profile.

iii. Deactivating Your Profile

If you would like to permanently deactivate your profile, go to the home page of the Site ([www.hellomusic.com](http://www.hellomusic.com/)), click on "login" and enter your user ID and password. Then, click on "Settings." In the "Profiles" section, select the item you wish to deactivate, click "Delete" and confirm and click "Save." We will remove your profile and content from the site so that users may not view it or search for it, but we may retain backup copies of your profile and content for our business records.

iv. Personally-Identifying Information Provided by our Affiliates and Business Partners

We may also obtain Personal Information about you from our affiliates and business partners, based on information that has been shared with or made available to them.

B. Use of Personally-Identifying Information

We may use the Personally-Identifiable Information that you submit for any purposes related to our business. We may combine Personally-Identifiable Information that you provide to us with Personally-Identifiable Information about you that we obtain from our affiliates and business partners.

C. Disclosure of Personally-Identifying Information

As described in Section 4(A) ("Collecting Personally–Identifying Information from Site Users"), users may, at their option, disclose their own Personally-Identifying Information by any means they choose. We will disclose Personally-Identifying Information in the following circumstances:

i. DMCA Infringement Notifications, Counter Notices, Notices of Violations of Site Terms of Service and Other Communications Directed to Us

By submitting a Digital Millennium Copyright Act ( **"DMCA"** ) Infringement Notification, Counter Notice or other communication (including communications about content stored on or transmitted through this Site), you consent to have this communication forwarded to the person or entity who stored or transmitted the content addressed by your communications in order to facilitate a prompt resolution. For notices other than DMCA Infringement Notifications and Counter Notices, upon request, we will edit out your name and contact information. However, DMCA Infringement Notifications and Counter Notices (including any Personally-Identifiable Information set forth in the notifications) will be forwarded as submitted to us without any deletions.

ii. Surveys

From time to time, we may also ask you to participate in surveys for our general business and marketing purposes. Any Personally-Identifying Information provided to us in connection with a survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in non-personally-identifying, aggregated form.

iii. Contests, Giveaways and other Promotions

From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with promotions will be subject to the terms of the promotion, not this Privacy Policy. You will be given the option to consent to the use of your Personally-Identifying Information at the time you sign up for the promotion. You will not be required to participate in any promotion.

iv. Employees, Third-Party Processors, Third-Party Service Providers and Third Party Affiliates

We will disclose Personally-Identifying Information to our employees, contractors, affiliates, distributors, dealers, vendors and suppliers who process Personally-Identifying Information on our behalf, participate with us in the provision or operation of this Site, provide you with services or make potential opportunities available to you.

v. By Law, to Protect Rights and to Comply with Our Policies

We disclose Personally-Identifying information if: (1) required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order; (2) we believe in our sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect against fraud, to protect the property or other rights of us or other users, third parties or the public at large; or (3) we believe that you have abused the service by using it to attack other systems or to gain unauthorized access to any other system, to engage in spamming or otherwise to violate applicable laws.

vi. Business Transfers; Bankruptcy

We reserve the right to transfer all Personally-Identifying Information in our possession to a successor entity in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of our assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personally-Identifying Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and you affirmatively opt-in to accept it. Personally-Identifying Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the successor entity.

vii. Marketing Communications

We may email you about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt-out of receiving marketing materials from us, please follow the instructions at the bottom of each email for opting out.

viii. Email Service

You may have the opportunity to use a service to send electronic mail to another user or email list. In such cases, your valid email address and real name will be included with such messages. In order to prevent abuse, you may not opt out of such a display, but you may choose to refrain from using this service to transmit an email message.

↑ Back to Top

Third parties are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy with respect to Personally-Identifying Information that you provide directly to those third parties or that those third parties collect for themselves. We do not control the third-party sites that may be accessible through this Site. Thus, this Privacy Policy does not apply to information provided to third-party sites or gathered by the third parties that operate them. Before visiting a third-party site, whether by means of a link on this Site or otherwise, and before providing any Personally-Identifying Information to any third party, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that site, and should take those steps necessary to your discretion, to protect your privacy.

↑ Back to Top

Because of changes in technology and the growth and development of our business, or for other business reasons, we may need to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will alert you by email if this policy is revised (if you have given us your email address), and we will post a copy of the new policy with its effective date on this Site. It is therefore important that you register with the site and notify us if you change your email address. If you do not provide us with a current email address, you should regularly review this policy to ensure that you are informed of any changes.

↑ Back to Top

####  Hello Music Deals Privacy Policy

Your privacy should remain private, so: We don't give your email address to third parties. We don't give your home address or credit card number away, either. But we want you to know a few things about how we handle information you give us.

Hello Music Deals collects information from you that we need in order to: process your order; provide you with member support; allow you to participate in the community and enter contests and other site features; and send you newsletters and other communications such as polls, surveys, and special Hello Music Deals offers. This information includes, but is not limited to: name, shipping and billing address, credit card number, e-mail address, etc.

Hello Music Deals will set and access our own cookies on your computer to allow you to make purchases and interact at the site. We also use web beacons to gather anonymous, aggregated statistical information (e.g. unique hits, page views, etc.) about our website traffic.

Hello Music Deals may share information collected by us with third parties to help process your order (e.g. shipping companies, credit card processors, etc.) or to provide statistical and demographic analysis to Hello Music Deals to help us and our business partners provide you with better services and offerings.

Hello Music Deals will not share, rent, lease, or sell your personal information (e.g. your e-mail address, your credit card information, your name, your address, etc.) to any third party for their independent use or benefit. Never! Ever!

Basically, this is all the same mumbo-jumbo that other sites put into more legal terms so you become confused and don't read it all. The difference between us and them is...we mean it.

Future changes to this Privacy Policy may be made at any time by sending you an email or posting notice of the changes on the site, with the changes effective 30 days after Hello Music Deals' dispatch of the email or posting of the notice. To ask questions about this policy or to remove your personal information from our database, write us at [privacy@hellomusic.com](mailto:privacy@hellomusic.com).

↑ Back to Top
